

TEL: 437-219-1549 E-mail: ei.matsuda.13@gmail.com

## Plofile

I'm an experienced front-end developer based in Toronto. I have an excellent ability to reproduce web design into website with high quality and effective motions for users. I've developed more than 300 pages in my career for 8 years and I've never lost deadlines. I'm good at developing website quickly, responsively, and accurately.

## Education

EF International Language Campuses Toronto

June 2021 - Februaly 2022

Chiba University, Graduate
School of Advanced
Integration Science
(Chiba, Japan) Master of
Engineering

April 2012 - March 2014

Chiba University, Faculty of Engineering (Chiba, Japan)
Department og Image Science
April 2008 - March 2012

## Experience

Rhino inc. (Tokyo, Japan) Front-end Developer

January 2017 - May 2021

- I have developed a lot of websites for any kind of client like a clothing brand, sports brand, and cosmetic brand.
- I renewed the fashion and lifestyle web magazine named HOUYHNHNM operated by Rhino inc and started in 2005. It has more than 1000 articles.

Ricoh, co.ltd, (Tokyo, Japan) Web application engineer

**April 2014 - January 2017** 

- Developing application related to digital photocopy machine with JAVA and Spring framework.

## Skills

Markup and programing

HTML | CSS | SASS | javascript | Vue | Nuxt.js | jQuery | npm | gulp | Node.js | PHP | Wordpress | API | Bootstrap | SVG | JAVA | Spring framework |

Tools

AdobeCC | AdobeXD | Figma | netlify

Language

Japanese (native) | English (Advanced)

**Business** 

Google Analytics | SEO |